Madeleine Harris

Atlanta, GA, 30309 | mmlh.harris@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/miss-mad/ | **Portfolio:** https://miss-mad.github.io/portfolio/ | **LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/madeleine-m-harris/

SUMMARY

Self-motivated full stack web developer with a unique and varied background in healthcare, retail, event coordination, property management, accounting, and the fine arts. This wide array of experience culminates in a meticulous, disciplined, and ever-inquisitive fast learner. Excited to bring new technical and development skills, combined with existing knowledge and skill, to this flourishing field of web development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Git, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6 and CommonJS), SQL, NoSQL, GraphQL **Frameworks:** CSS Frameworks (Materialize CSS, Bootstrap CSS), Express, MySQL **Libraries:** jQuery, Sequelize, MongoDB and Mongoose, Apollo, React, Ant Design **Core Concepts:** Mobile-First Design, Local and Session Storage, APIs (client, third-party, and server-side), User Authentication, Agile Methodology, Github and Heroku Deployment

PROJECTS

ResuMade

https://github.com/PeytonCast/ResuMade | http://resumade.herokuapp.com/

- Easily create professional resumes here
- Role: React form + ant design
- Tools: React, Stripe, JavaScript, Express, Apollo, GraphQL, MongoDB, jsonwebtoken

Who's App

https://github.com/miss-mad/Whos-App | https://whooos-app.herokuapp.com/

- The newest anonymous and secure messaging app is here! Who is it you'll be talking to?
- Role: Project manager + Socket.io
- Tools: Socket.io, JavaScript, Node, Express, Sequelize, MySQL, Handlebars, Bootstrap

MTHSY Music

https://github.com/miss-mad/mthsy-music | https://miss-mad.github.io/mthsy-music/

- A one-stop shop for music information and upcoming events for music artists
- Role: lastFM API + local storage
- Tools: JavaScript, HTML, Materialize CSS, APIs: lastFM, YouTube, TicketMaster

EXPERIENCE

Pharmacy Technician

2021 - Present

Walgreens Marietta, GA

Highly communicative to 100s of patients of all ages to ensure timely medication requests' fulfillment while efficiently taking in new prescriptions, filling existing orders, and checking out waiting patients. Meticulously sorted the day's incoming medicine order to ensure out of stock items are completed. while also coordinating various vaccine appointments and COVID testing.

CME Coordinator 2019 – 2020

American Medical Forum

Alpharetta, GA

Built 15 new events into the company website via Wordpress and WooCommerce. Repeatedly coordinated periodic nationwide medical conferences with 100s of healthcare professional attendees. Facilitated participant experience from registration to the CME credit claiming process by email, phone, and chat.

Licensed Property Manager

2018 - 2019

HomeOwners Advantage

Atlanta, GA

Project manager for the \$143,691 gym renovation June – September 2018. Attended and minuted bi-monthly evening Board and Finance Committee meetings. Oversaw the master association and the 7-member concierge team while routinely surveilling the property, organizing necessary maintenance and repairs.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development: Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, GA, 2022 **Bachelor of Arts:** Cum Laude with Honors, Kennesaw State University, Kennesaw, GA